[indistinct chatter]
I'm starving.
Yeah, we gotta fuel up first!
What do you feel like eating?
Baked potato!
[Nagisa chuckles] Oh, nice.
What about takoyaki?
[exclaims] Guys, look!
Everybody, check it out!
[Mariko] Aren't they first-years
at our school?
[Sana] I wonder if they're on a date!
Aww, she's wearing a yukata!
Her hair is really cute, too!
[Akari] I love their rom-com vibes!
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 12
GIRLS...
[Taiki] She's so quiet.
She's never been this quiet
around me for this long.
- I'm gonna go get some yakisoba!
- Huh?
Oh, if you're buying stuff, I'll come--
[gasps softly]
[Hina] This whole situation
has me nervous.
I did want it to be just the two of us.
But Kyo cancelling last-minute
caught me off-guard.
Just us?
[groans]
I'M STILL IN
[girls laughing]
[girl] I've kinda been pigging out.
[Hina] I wonder
if my lip gloss is everywhere.
I did eat a candy apple.
Do my bangs look okay?
I hope my obi's not crooked.
[sighs]
YAKISOBA
500 YEN
- Truth is, I really want him to see me.
- Hi there!
- That'll be exactly...
- I went to all this trouble
so if there's any chance,
I want him to think I look pretty.
But at the same time,
what if I look weird?
I never dress like this,
so I feel a little self-conscious.
I want to get his attention,
but then I don't.
[Taiki] Here looks good!
- Watch out for rocks and stuff.
- Thank you.
Looks like we still have ten minutes.
Yeah, you're right.
Want anything to drink?
Uh, no, thanks.
[Taiki] I thought this was
just a normal thing,
but she's definitely acting weird.
[mosquito buzzing]
[grunts]
[Taiki] It's the mosquitoes.
- [Hina sighs]
- And it looks like they already got her.
[bag crinkling]
Here. I have this.
Mm-mm.
Thanks, Taiki.
[Taiki] Must be itchy.
Wait, you'll stain your yukata like that.
Let me.
You needed to go a bit more left.
Uh, this is more awkward
than I thought it'd be.
Oh. She missed a strand...
- So did you do your hair yourself?
- Hm?
Yeah, I did.
Why?
It's pretty intricate,
so I'm a bit surprised.
You're mocking me?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I'm, like, genuinely impressed.
Well, it sounds like
you're trying to provoke me!
Oh, no! No, I missed a piece!
I knew you were being sarcastic.
You're taking it all wrong.
I can tell it wasn't easy,
and you did your best.
I thought it looked cute,
so I complimented you.
[Hina] Wait. "Cute"?
[gasps] Say that again!
[exclaims softly]
[all applauding]
Oh, there's no pre-show.
[firecrackers continue bursting]
[chuckles]
Cute. Just saying one word
can make them so happy.
Girls...
[woman on PA] There will now be
a 20-minute intermission.
Hey, I'm just gonna run to the bathroom.
Yep. I'll watch our stuff.
[chuckles] He said I looked cute.
[Taiki] Looks like I beat the crowd.
Maybe I'll grab a drink.
I wonder if Hina wants something.
[Chinatsu] Are you lost?
- Oh, honey, you can't find your mom?
- [crying]
You fell down, too, huh?
Let's go to the front
and get some first aid.
It's okay. It's okay.
Pain, pain, go away.
Go away!
- Oh.
- [Taiki] Um...
- Is she lost?
- Mm-hm.
I think that she and her mom
got separated.
I thought that I would
take her up to the main booth.
Let me help you.
What?
Mind if I tag along?
Oh, no, don't worry, I can handle it!
I'm going that direction anyway.
- What's your name?
- Yume.
[Taiki] Hello, Yume!
I hate to keep Hina waiting,
but I can't not help.
[Yume] Wait!
We're all going together!
[Hina] Good!
I can't stand mosquitoes, usually.
But today, they did me a solid.
I thought that it looked cute.
[laughs]
- [boy] Chono?
- Hm?
[Ito exclaims softly]
Ito, hi.
I didn't know you'd be here.
You're alone?
Wait. No, of course you aren't.
You here with teammates?
Ah, no. I'm actually here with Taiki.
Taiki?
Yeah, Kyo was supposed
to be part of our group,
but he came down with something.
And another person said
she already had plans with other friends!
Then... let's combine groups.
Fireworks are more fun to watch
in a bigger group.
Our legs are sour from standing,
and to be honest,
we would love a place to sit down.
What do you say?
Hey, Yume, are you feeling thirsty at all?
[Yume] No, thank you!
[Chinatsu] Okay. It's not too far,
so let's keep going.
[Yume] 'Kay.
[Taiki] I didn't expect Chinatsu
to be so good with kids.
Maybe 'cause I only hear her
talk with upperclassmen.
Oh, I'm sorry.
All good.
Whoa, this woman's beautiful.
- Are you okay?
- [Chinatsu] Karen!
Chii!
You two know each other?
Of course! Karen's my best friend!
She and I went
to the same elementary school.
[Taiki] What a school that must've been!
Well, hi there.
Good evening!
- She's Haryu's girlfriend.
- What's your name?
Yume!
Really?
- Are you here with Haryu?
- Yeah. He's in the seating area.
[Taiki] What?
He did say he had a girlfriend
in show business.
By the way...
who's this?
Hello.
My name is Taiki Inomata.
Haryu's really looked out
for me this year.
Wait, Inomata! Like, the "Taiki Inomata"?
- Well, well, well! So you're him!
- Um...
[Taiki] "The"?
What kind of things
has Haryu been saying about me?
Huh?
Oh...
He, um...
said that you've got nerves of steel.
[Taiki] No freakin' way.
- Well, then, I'm going to scoot.
- [Yume] Huh?
[Karen chuckles]
Makes sense
that she is Haryu's girlfriend.
Yep. They're a good match.
[Karen chuckles]
I'm glad I stumbled into that!
- [Karen] Kengo! Guess what?
- Hm?
I have to tell you what I just saw!
What was it?
I bumped into Taiki Inomata
and Chii just now!
Just the two of them?
Well, there were three, to be precise.
It didn't look like
they were on a date, though.
Seems like a good kid.
Taiki Inomata.
They should get together already.
I just don't think
that's where her head is at.
Ah, makes sense.
What's up?
If you ever start
to slack off in badminton,
I am gonna end this!
Yes, I'm aware of that, Karen.
My heart's with you and badminton.
[Karen] That's what I wanna hear!
It does seem like Chii is really
overthinking some things in her life.
FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
[man] You're lost?
Gosh, her mother was just here
a minute ago.
She went off to go look again.
I'll make an announcement now.
I'll look for her mom!
Why don't the two of you stay right here.
I'll be back!
Why don't we wait inside the booth, okay?
RECEPTION
That lady we met... Her yukata was pretty.
Yeah, it was.
It had so many flowers, it was super cute!
So you didn't wanna wear one? A yukata?
Mmmm...
Only a bit.
Then again, this T-shirt
is one of my absolute favorites.
Don't you think
the design is pretty, Yume?
That's your best shirt?
- You have more refined style than I do.
- [laughs]
But I guess...
the best clothing I own is my uniform.
Yoo-mi-form?
It's what you wear when
you're playing a sport. I play basketball.
I know basketball!
[Chinatsu] Wearing that uniform...
It makes me want to be
the coolest version of myself.
[Karen] What?
You're living with a first-year boy?
We're cohabitating.
That's literally the same thing!
Don't you get self-conscious?
Like, when he looks manly...
or does something you like?
Yeah, I do.
But...
Looking for Yume's mother! Yume's mother?
I'm awkward
when it comes to things like this.
Wearing a yukata is just too much.
[gasps] I know, right?
Huh?
I was trying to put on my yukata
all by myself!
But it got messy, you know?
And my mom ended up
having to help me get dressed!
[laughs]
It is tricky, huh?
[Taiki] Hey!
[Yume's mother panting]
Yume!
Mama!
- Mama! [cries]
- Where have you been?
Mama!
She heard the announcement,
so it was easy to find her.
What a relief.
Really. I cannot thank you enough.
Is there something that I can...
Oh, not at all!
Stick to your mom like glue.
[exclaims softly]
Yume?
Hold on!
[clicking]
It's for you!
[exclaims]
Dressing up in a yukata is hard...
but wearing a clip is simple!
You look way more stylish now!
But it...
Ah could you keep it, please?
It would mean a lot to her!
[giggles]
I'd be glad to.
[Yume] Bye-bye!
Come on, let's go.
- [Taiki laughs]
- What are you laughing at?
[Taiki] Oh, no, I'm not...
[continues laughing]
You're being a butthead.
You're ruining her kind gesture.
[Taiki] And it looks great.
In fact, I hope you wear it
all the time now.
[Chinatsu groans]
[Taiki laughs]
[Chinatsu] You're laughing again.
[Taiki] Well, you're just
silently staring at me.
And make sure you wear it till we're home.
'Cause she'll get bummed out,
if she sees you later
and you're not wearing it.
I'm gonna keep it on, obviously.
She helped me look fashionable,
and it won't be in vain.
[Taiki chuckles]
Then why don't I take your photo?
[Chinatsu] I do not consent.
[Taiki] I didn't consent at the aquarium.
If I told Chinatsu right now,
that I think she looks cute...
I'm sure there'd be a pause...
and then she'd say
"thank you" to be polite...
and then all the fun of the night
would come to an end.
[firecrackers bursting]
[all cheering, applauding]
[Chinatsu gasps]
[Chinatsu] Intermission's over.
[Taiki] Yeah.
You should be getting back.
Nagisa and the others
are waiting for me, too.
[Taiki] Yeah, you're right.
Then I'll see you at home.
Yeah. See you.
[Taiki running, panting]
Dang. I left Hina waiting
way longer than I meant to.
Come and get a knuckle sandwich.
Got it, punk?
[Taiki] It's just us two,
and I left her alone. I gotta apologize.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
I'm sorry. That was a long time.
You're gonna owe me.
Ah, I don't like that.
While I was gone, was everything okay?
Yeah.
The food stands are great.
The fireworks are beautiful.
This is the best!
We should come again next year.
Yeah, we should.
[Hina] What I really meant
when I said that
was "just the two of us again."
[Sana] Hey, Chinatsu, you're back.
Where'd you get that barrette from?
[Chinatsu] It's a long story.
By the way, Chii... why do you look so sad?
[exclaims softly]
[Taiki] What is next year
going to look like for all of us?
A year is a long time.
What's going to change
between now and then?
Those questions come and go,
just like the fireworks
in the night's sky.
[insects trilling]
Morning, Yukiko.
Morning, Chinatsu.
You are right on time for breakfast.
Oh, is Taiki up already?
He went out on a run.
He's just raring
to go first thing in the morning!
He said the practice the other day
made him realize
how much he needs to work on his stamina,
so he was all fired up!
[inspiring music playing]
[ball dribbling]
[player] Heads up!
[pants]
[whistle blows]
Natsu, you could've made that pass
back there to Nagisa instead.
She didn't have anyone on her.
Keep a cool head,
even when we're short on time.
Right.
I know that nationals are coming up soon,
but don't let them
interfere with your playing.
Just do your thing, you know?
You've got this in the bag, Chinatsu.
I guarantee it.
Okay!
Yeah!
Another day another win.
[boy 2] We're not even close
to the same level anymore.
[boy 1] Yeah, I mean,
he did qualify for nationals.
[Taiki] At practice the other day...
the gap between Haryu and Hyodo's scores
was smaller than it was
at prefectural qualifiers.
There are two slots
for nationals next year.
My money's on Haryu and Yusa to go.
If you'd swung like that before,
you could've scored more points on Yusa.
Want some?
[scoffs]
Kyo, feed me some shuttles!
Huh?
[Taiki] Having Hyodo
say something like that...
makes me want to work as hard as they do.
Whoa, Kyo! That's a bit fast!
Excuse me! I just gotta grab the shuttle!
Hina, it came pretty clo--
[humming, singing softly]
Keep it up.
- Did you not hear that?
- Huh?
Huh? Hear what?
[sighs]
- This is what I'm talking about.
- Huh?
[Niina] Never mind. Don't change, friend.
[Hina] Wait I wanna know!
[balls dribbling, sneakers skidding]
[Kikuchi] Let's take lunch!
We'll be back again at 1:20!
[girls] Okay!
- [exclaims]
- I'll open some windows.
You're the best.
[exclaims softly]
[snoring]
Taiki?
You asleep?
He did go for a run this morning.
He cuddles his tracksuit when he sleeps.
DOESN'T USE IT AS A BLANKET...
Hello.
Mr. Inomata.
There's something that I wanted
to ask you the other day.
You and Hina...
Have the two of you started going out?
How you answer will determine the feelings
I have about being your housemate.
I guess it's obvious they're dating.
They went
to the fireworks festival together.
And I already know
that Hina has a crush on Taiki.
[mellow music playing]
If you are dating...
I wish you would've said so.
Are you going to go to the festival?
Yeah, with some friends.
[Chinatsu] You didn't have to do that.
Lie about going with friends.
If you would've told me, then I...
Knowing you lied to me...
I can't help but feel sad.
[wind blowing]
[grunts softly]
[yawns]
Ah, that was a great nap.
It almost feels like someone was here...
But maybe...
I imagined it.
[closing theme song playing]